

+46 762 876 674

- zhuhuadan@gmail.com
- https://zhuhuadan.com https://github.com/MikoZhu
- Stockholm, Sweden

EDUCATION

Master of HR Business and Management Aston University(UK) 2017 - 2018

Bachelor of Foreign Trade Jiangsu University of Technology(CHINA) 2007 - 2011

Python and C#

Hermods Yrkeshögskola Mar 2021 - Sep 2021

Full-Stack Bootcamp Udemy Sep 2022 - Sep 2023

EXPERTISE

HTML CSS/SCSS Tailwind Javascript React Node.js Express.js MongoDB Agile Methodology Figma Canva Photoshop

LANGUAGE

English Swedish(SVA 2) Chinese

HUADAN ZHU

Front-end || Full-Stack developer

ABOUT ME

I am embarking on a career transition from the field of HRM to web development. With a master's degree in HRM and seven years of experience in human resources management, I have developed strong skills in adaptability, a growth mindset, and the confidence to tackle new challenges. As a web developer, I am excited to leverage these qualities to solve complex problems, continue exploring new skills, and further improve as a developer.

EXPERIENCE

O June 2023- Jan 2024

Technigo, Sweden

Web Development Bootcamp

A 22-week fast-paced remote Boot Camp and more than 500 hours coding, focusing on JavaScript (ES6), React, HTML5, CSS, and server-side programming with Node.js, with weekly projects covering everything from the basics of programming to structuring web projects using the latest technology.

Dec 2020 - Sep 2021 SHEIN

Client Service

At SHEIN, a fast fashion company, I achieved a 98% customer satisfaction rate. Proficient in CSM, I managed 60+ daily tickets with 99% accuracy, emphasizing seamless Swedish customer experiences in logistics and returns.

Sep 2017 - Sep 2019

UCNEST

Marketing and Recruiter

At a startup tech company, I recruited and trained over 30 professionals, catalyzing organizational growth. In the realm of Marketing & Customer Service, I achieved 100% sales success with a 10% contribution from customer service while expanding into the Chinese market through trend-savvy, multichannel strategies.

Aug 2014 - Oct 2016

World International English

Regional HR Manager

Screened over 100 candidates and conducted 20 phone interviews daily, resulting in the recruitment of 500+ professionals, including key leaders. Orchestrated coaching programs to foster growth and aligned HR with strategic management to achieve business goals.

Feb 2013 - Jun 2014

SRE Group

HR Supervisor

Managed HR across multiple locations, overseeing monthly interviews for 150+ candidates and achieving annual onboarding exceeding 100. Implemented competitive reward and payroll strategy, executed organization-wide HR functions, integrating KPIs, 360 assessments, SMART goals, and a performance management system.